

Executive Summary

IT specialist with 4+ years of professional experience in information security and digital forensics. Expert with a wide variety of security, engineering, networking, and operating system software.

Languages

English - Intermediated

Bengali - Native

Hindi - Listening

Skills



OMAR FARUK SANY

A Professional Web Designer & IT Expert

☑ omarfaruk180859@gmail.com

0 01854112404

Comilla, Bangladesh

WORK EXPERIENCE

CEO 01-01-2019 - Till Now

Dream 71 IT Corner, Cumilla, Bangladesh.

Customer service representative supports customers by providing helpful information, answering questions, and responding to complaints. They're the front line of support for clients and customers and they help ensure that customers are satisfied with products, services, and features.

WEB DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER Online & Offline (Upwork, Freelancer)

01-06-2017-Till Now

- * Worked with internal and external facing system to build UI experiences.
- ** Led multiple projects develpoing front and software using framework PHP, Laravel.
- *** Used HTML, CSS, and Javascript also.

FREELANCER

10-05-2018 - Till Now

Freelancer.com , Bangladesh.

WEB DESIGNER 01-05-2018 - Till Now

Upwork Bangladesh Ltd., Dhaka, Bangladesh

NETWORK TECHNICIAN 01-01-2018 - 01-01-2019

Hossain IT Ltd., Brahmanbaria, Bangladesh.

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN 01-01-2018 - 01-01-2018

Mujumdar IT Ltd., Cumilla, Bangladesh.

SALESMAN 10-06-2018 - 10-10-2018

Apex Bangladesh Ltd., Cumilla.

Services customers by selling products and meeting customer needs. Services existing accounts, obtains orders, and establishes new accounts by planning and organizing daily work schedule to call on existing or potential sales outlets and other trade factors.

TEACHER 11--01-2015-30-12-2018

Cumilla Mission School & College, Cumilla Bangladesh.

Teacher is responsible for preparing lesson plans and educating students at all levels. Their duties include assigning homework, grading tests, and documenting progress. Teachers must be able to instruct in a variety of subjects and reach students with engaging lesson plans.

MEMBER 01-12-2017 - Till Now

Durbar Foundation, Cumilla, Bangladesh.

For improving own skill.

MEMBER 01-01-2017 - Till Now

10 minitue School, Dhaka, Bangladesh

CO-ORDINATE 10-07-2018 - Till Now

University Poem & Dibeting Club, Lalmai University College, Cumilla, Bangladesh

Out of Office



*Social Activities & Volunteer

**I like this activity because Volunteering connects you to others Even helping out with the smallest tasks can make a real difference to the lives of people, animals, and organizations in need.

***It benefit me Dedicating my time as a volunteer helps me make new friends, expand my network, and boost my social skills.



SEO



Like to teach someone



Investigation



Mentorship





Sing Sono



. .



Volunteering



Help Another



Love Playing



Photography



Reading

Certification

Web Developer

Shek Kamal IT Training & Incubation Center Project,ICT Division Bangladesh.

Web Designer

Learning & Earning Development Project, ICT Division Bangladesh.

Student of the Year Comilla Disterict 2017,2018 Natinal Educational Authority

Reading & Writing Test British Council BD

Science Participant Comilla University Science Festivle

Math Participant Bangladesh Math Olilmpiad

COURSES

LARAVEL-PHP - Sheke Kamal IT Training & Incubantion Center Project

WEB DESIGN & DEVELPOMENT - IT Vision Ltd. Bangladesh

PHP LANGUAGE - Sheke Kamal IT Training & Incubantion Center Project

ENGLISH SPEAKING & LISTENING - Sheke Kamal IT Training & Incubantion Center Project

READING & WRITING - Sheke Kamal IT Training & Incubantion Center Project

LEADERSHIP - Online -10 Minitue School
COMMUNICATION SKILL - 10 Minitue School

CV WRITING - Mukthopath Online

MS WORD, EXCEL, POWERPOINT, INTERNET BROWSING - Ict Division, Cumilla.

GRAPHIC DESIGN - IT Vision Ltd., Cumilla PRESENTION SKILL - 10 Minitue School

DEBATE - 10 Minute School

PHOTOGRAPHY COURSE - Mukthopath.com (Online)

EDUCATION

DATA ANALAYSIS
Online - W3 School

GRAPHIC DESIGN
ICT Division Bangladesh
20-01-2020 - Till Now

WEB DESIGN ICT Division Bangladesh 20-01-2020 - Till Now

HONOURS 3RD YEAR Lalmai Govt. University College 10-10-2018 - Till Now

HIGHER SECONDARY Govt. Bangabandhu College, Cumilla, Bangladesh 10-07-2015 - 10-04-2017

SECONDARY

Police Line High School, Cumilla, Bangladesh. 01-01-2010 -10-05-2015

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Certificate Name : Omar Faruk Fathers Name : Abdul Alim Mother's Name : Shamsunahar

Address: West Bagichagoan, Cumilla, Bangladesh.

Date of Birth : 31-12-1999 Home District : Cumilla Maritual Status : Single Height : 5 Feet 6 Inchee Gender : Male

Nationality: Bangladesh

Religion : Islam

Scan the QR code to view my online resume with more information about my career.

